RG 002:025, Government Administration and Policy Committee
Connecticut State Library
Government Administration and Policy Committee records
1911-1978
bulk 1976-1978
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. General Assembly. Government Administration and Policy Committee
2 cubic feet
Submissions for the Connecticut State Song competition. Records include letters of submission, lyrics, sheet music, and sound recordings.
RG002_025_GAP
T001464
Scope and Content
Submissions for the Connecticut State Song competition. The records include letters of submission, lyrics, sheet music, and sound recordings collected in the 1970's during a competition that allowed composers to submit their version of a possible state song.
Arrangement
The records are arranged alphabetically by title or song and type of document.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. General Assembly. Government Administration and Policy Committee
Subjects:
Connecticut. General Assembly. Government Administration and Policy Committee -- Records and correspondence
Document Types:
Sound Recordings; Clippings; Correspondence; Sheet Music; Songs (document genre)
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Series 1. Papers Relating to the Selection of a State Song, 1911-1978; bulk 1976-1978
  - A, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Adventures Along the Connecticut Coast, Re Circo, 1973-1977
      Sound recording removed to a separate box.
    - American, Mrs. William Liska, 1977
  - C, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - The Charter of Connecticut and Our Connecticut, Camille Beaulieu, 1973-1974
    - Christmas In Connecticut, Sid Atkinson, 1974
    - Coastal Connecticut Waters, Alfred Nesbit, 1973-1977
    - Come To Connecticut, Alfred Nesbit, 1973
    - Come To Connecticut, George Wedberg, 1977
  - C, 1932-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Connecticut, Paul Alpert, 1977
    - Connecticut, John Fico, undated
    - Connecticut, Clayton Hotchkiss, 1932-1977
  - C, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Connecticut, Isabele Jensen, 1974-1977
    - Connecticut, Arthur Nelson, 1978
    - Connecticut, Fred O'Connor, 1974
    - Connecticut, Michael S. Reale Sr., 1977
  - C, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Connecticut Anthem, Judson Moore, 1976-1977
    - Connecticut, Connecticut, undated
    - Connecticut, Forever a Home for the Robin, David Harvey, 1977
    - Connecticut is my Homeland, Robert LaRocco, 1973-1975
  - C, 1911-1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Connecticut March, William Nassann, 1911-1973
    - Connecticut, My Home, Ed Bednarski, 1977
    - Connecticut, My Home, John J. Ferguson, 1972
    - Connecticut, My Home, Guy Louis, 1973
  - C, 1969-1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Connecticut's Peoples, Michael Grigaitis, undated
    - The Connecticut Song, Joseph Grestick, 1972
    - Connecticut State Song, Dana Briggs, undated
    - Connecticut's The Place To Be!, Ted Howes, 1974-1977
    - Connecticut, U.S.A., Guy Louis, 1974
    - Connecticut Welcomes You, Libbie E. Richmond, 1969-1975
  - C, 1964-1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - The Connecticut Yankee March, Catherine Auth, 1975-1976
    - The Connecticut Year, Richard Schooner, 1978
    - Constitution State, Eric A. Osterling, 1964-1977
  - C-G, 1962-1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - A Corner Called Connecticut, Paul Munson Jr., 1973
    - Correspondence, Multiple, 1977-1978
    - Dear Old Connecticut, Stephen Ondek, 1962-1976
    - The Freedom Song, Joeseph Leniado-Chira, 1963-1977
    - God Loves This Land of Ours, Joseph S. Russo, 1973
  - H, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Hail Connecticut, Bill Fredericks, 1977
    - Hail Connecticut, Albert Hurwit, 1977
    - Hail Connecticut, Doris Sassano, undated
    - Hail to the State of Connecticut, Rolan Wattson, undated
    - Heritage Dub, undated
    - Hills of My Connecticut, Mike Rice, undated
    - Honor and Glory, Edith J. Coffey, undated
  - I, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - I'll Never Forget Connecticut, Fay Gelbman, undated
    - Index Cards, undated
    - In Praise of Connecticut, Jonathan Turner, 1977
  - L-P, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - A Little Old Hut In Connecticut, Ray Beckett, undated
    - Natural Wonderland, Mark Scarpelli, undated
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1976-1978
    - Notes, Dorothy Osler, 1975
    - Proudly I Sing, Steve Zanowiac, 1974
  - S, 1972-1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Salute To Connecticut, Milla Doyle, 1977-1978
    - Sing Out Thy Praise of Connecticut, Sylvia Lee Chaly, 1977
    - Song For Connecticut, Debra Labonte, undated
    - Song of Connecticut, Arden Clar, 1972-1977
  - T-W, 1973-1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - There Is Something Kinda Nice About Connecticut, Charlie Murray, 1976-1977
    - Unidentified Recording, undated
    - The Walls Beneath the Trees, Andrew S. Ward, undated
    - We're Proud of Connecticut, James A. Pennypacker, 1973-1977
    - Why Didn't They Write A Song About Connecticut, Lanny Grey, 1978
  - Y, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - The Yankee Bicentennial Songbook, Paul Munson, 1976
  - Sound Recordings, 1964-1978; These items are separated from the records. Please contact State Archives staff for assistance.
    - The Charter of Connecticut and Our Connecticut, circa 1973-1974; 1 sound cassette (Box 3)
    - Christmas in Connecticut and We Love you Connecticut, 1974; 2 sound cassettes (Box 3)
    - Connecticut, John Fico, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 3)
    - Connecticut, Clayton Hotchkiss, circa 1977; 1 sound cassette (Box 3)
    - Connecticut, Arthur Nelson, 1978; 1 sound cassette (Box 3)
    - Connecticut, Fred O'Connor, 1974; 1 sound cassette (Box 3)
    - Connecticut, Michael Reale, 1977; 1 sound cassette (Box 3)
    - Connecticut, Forever A Home For The Robin, 1977; 1 sound cassette (Box 3)
    - Connecticut Is My Homeland, Robert LaRocco, circa 1975; 1 sound cassette (Box 3)
    - Connecticut, My Home, Ed Bednarski, 1977; 1 sound tape reel (Box 3)
    - Connecticut, My home, John Ferguson, 1972; 1 sound cassette (Box 3)
    - Connecticut, My Home, Guy Louis, 1973; 1 sound tape reel (Box 3)
    - Connecticut's People, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 3)
    - Connecticut, U.S.A., 1974; 1 sound tape reel (Box 3)
    - Connecticut Yankee March, circa 1975-1976; 2 sound cassettes (Box 3)
    - Connecticut Year, 1978; 1 sound cassette (Box 3)
    - Constitution State, circa 1964-1977; 1 sound cassette (Box 3)
    - Hills of My Connecticut, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 4)
    - I'll Never Forget Connecticut, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 4)
    - Natural Wonderland, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 4)
    - Proudly I Sing, 1974; 1 sound cassette (Box 4)
    - Salute To Connecticut, circa 1977; 1 sound cassette (Box 4)
    - Unidentified Recording, undated; 1 sound tape reel (Box 4)
    - Why Didn't They Write A Song About Connecticut, 1978; 1 sound cassette (Box 4)
    - Coastal Connecticut Waters and Come to Connecticut, circa 1973-1977; 2 sound tape reels (Box 5)
    - Connecticut State Song, undated; 1 sound tape reel (Box 5)
    - Connecticut's The Place to Be, circa 1974-1977; 1 sound tape reel (Box 5)
    - Connecticut Welcomes You, circa 1969-1975; 1 sound tape reel (Box 5)
    - Corner Called Connecticut, 1973; 1 sound tape reel (Box 5)
    - Hail Connecticut, Bill Fredricks, 1977; 1 sound tape reel (Box 5)
    - Hail Connecticut, Albert Hurwit, 1977; 1 sound tape reel (Box 5)
    - Hail to the State of Connecticut, undated; 1 sound tape reel (Box 5)
    - Heritage Dub, undated; 1 sound tape reel (Box 5)
    - Song For Connecticut, undated; 1 sound tape reel (Box 5)
    - The Walls Beneath the Trees, undated; 1 sound tape reel (Box 5)
    - Adventures Along the Connecticut Coast, circa 1973-1977; 3 vinyl recordings (Box Shared audio disc box)
    - The Charter of Connecticut and Our Connecticut, 1973-1974; 2 vinyl recordings
    - Connecticut if my Homeland, circa 1975; 1 vinyl recording
    - The Connecticut Song, 1972; 1 vinyl recording
    - Connecticut's The Place to Be, circa 1974-1977; 3 vinyl recordings
    - God Loves This Land of Ours, 1973; 1 vinyl recording
    - There's Something Kinda Nice About Connecticut, circa 1976-1977; 1 vinyl recording
    - Yankee Bicentennial Songbook, Herons at Sunset, 1976; 1 vinyl recording